This setup makes your iPhone into a mini
computer. I've set up my iPhone to
basically replace my computer when I'm
not at home. First is the magic stand.
[music] Not only is it the thinnest
MagSafe stand I've ever seen, it also
gives you the most optimal view angle,
and [music] it just collapses and kind
of disappears into your phone. This is a
folding keyboard made by the company
[music] iClever. This keyboard fits in
your back pocket. There are a bunch of
keyboard shortcuts already built into
iOS, and they're pretty much exactly
[music] the same as macOS, so it's
really easy to learn. The battery life
is surprisingly long, and once you
collapse it, it immediately goes into
sleep mode. [music] At this point in the
setup, I know what you're thinking. You
can now connect your mouse to your
phone, and there's actually [music] a
cursor. A lot of times I'll just bring
the two of them and put them in my
sling, and I basically have a setup that
I can [music] do work for as many hours
as I need.